xusenet.com 2019-04-11

# 

#### Privacy Policy

Xusenet respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use Xusenet's services ("AUBA"). Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

**Xusenet and Cookies**

After your first login to Xusenet, Xusenet sends a "cookie" to your browser. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. Xusenet uses cookies to improve the quality of our service. Xusenet does this by storing user identification in cookies. In Xusenet's advance mode, other cookies has been used to store users' preferences. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the Xusenet service may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

Xusenet does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. 

**What Access Logs Do We Keep?**

Xusenet doesn't keep any access logs. However, for Xusenet's protection, access violation log will be reviewed regularly and purged. All other logs will be removed by automated system programs.

**With Whom Does Xusenet Share Information?**

Xusenet may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. Please be aware, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

**Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy**

By using the Xusenet Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. Xusenet may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Who can I ask if I have additional questions?**

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is [support@xusenet.com](mailto:support@xusenet.com).
